When Sonja Detrinidad opened her online shop selling houseplants, she didn’t have high hopes for it.
索尼娅·德特里尼达开网店卖室内绿植时，对它并没有抱太大希望。
But the opposite happened: She was flooded, shipping out 1,200 orders in June of 2020 alone.
但结果恰恰相反：订单如潮水般涌来，仅2020年6月一个月她就发出了1200份订单。
In the past year, Detrinidad sent out more than 70,000 plants.
在过去一年里，德特里尼达卖出了7万多盆植物。
Her success is just one example of increased time at home leading to an explosion in the houseplant industry.
她的成功只是一个例子，说明居家时间增多引发了室内植物行业的爆发式增长。
“Plants are in fashion right now,” says Dr. Melinda Knuth, a researcher from the University of Florida.
“植物现在很流行，”佛罗里达大学的研究员梅林达·努斯博士说。
“People who live in plant-rich environments report a higher life satisfaction rating,” she says.
“生活在绿植丰富环境中的人，报告的生活满意度更高，”她说。
“Adding more nature to our environment can change our mood and how we think.”
“给我们的环境增添更多自然元素，可以改变我们的情绪和思维方式。”
Plants can improve our state of mind in a few ways but the biggest is by decreasing our level of cortisol, the stress hormone in our body.
植物可以从几个方面改善我们的精神状态，但最主要的一点是降低体内的压力激素——皮质醇的水平。
“Students who are around plants perform better academically than students who are in a classroom without plants,” says Knuth.
“身边有植物的学生，学习成绩比在没有植物的教室里的学生更好，”努斯说。
“This productivity also translates into the workplace for adults.
“对成年人来说，这种效率的提升同样体现在工作场所。
Our study showed that there was a 30% decrease in sick leave for people who were in plant-rich workplaces.”
我们的研究表明，在绿植丰富的工作场所，人们的病假减少了30%。”
If you’re among the groups of people who are enjoying the mental and physical health benefits of surrounding yourself with plants, don’t beat yourself up if one (or a few!) doesn’t make it.
如果你也属于那些正在享受被植物环绕所带来的身心健康益处的人，那么当一盆（或几盆！）没养活时，不要责怪自己。
“Doctors practice medicine and lawyers practice law and you should allow yourself the practice it takes to sustain a plant.
“医生要行医，律师要从事法律工作，你也应该允许自己经历养活一株植物所需的练习。
Tending to plants is an exercise in patience and learning.
照料植物是一种关于耐心和学习的锻炼。
Be invested in taking care of it, but if it dies, go get another one,” Detrinidad says.
用心照顾它，但如果它死了，就再去买一盆，”德特里尼达说。